ILGWU David Dubinsky Foundation Records 5780/104
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 1974 Awards. Requests [Part 2 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 9)
  Appeals to the foundation, requests for grants, pamphlets and correspondence. Includes various reports and proposals from a wide array of organizations.
- 1974 Awards. Requests [Part 3 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 1974 Awards. Requests [Part 4 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 1974 Awards. Requests [Part 5 of 5] (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Agenda for April 2nd 1976 Meeting (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Beth Israel Medical Center, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  A proposal to the foundation, and a thank you correspondence.
- Chicano Education Project, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Proposal. November 20, 1978.
- Citizens Research Foundation (CRF), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  Appeal to the foundation. December 21st, 1971
- City of Hope, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  Appeal to the foundation and pamphlets regarding a pilot medical center.
- Copies of Request Summaries (Box 3, Folder 18)
  List and reviews of organizations requested grants. Copies are undated.
- Correspondence from Grant Recipients, 1968-1971 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  Thank you correspondence, updates, newsletters, news articles, photos, and reports.
- Correspondence regarding Second Board of Trustees Meeting, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  Agendas, reminders, and invitations.
- Correspondence to David Dubinsky, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  Letters of various topics.
- Creation of the David Dubinsky Foundation, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  Information on the founding the organization, the beginning, the biography of Dubinsky, statements of purpose, and bylaws.
- David Dubinsky Foundation. Board of Trustees Meeting, 1968-1970 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  1968 - 1970 Schedule of Awards. Includes clippings about grants, correspondence, and reports.
- Foundation Library Center, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  Inquiry about the DD Foundation, pamphlets, and questionnaires.
- The Hawthorne Studies, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Pamphlet regarding the Hawthorne Studies.
- Hudson Institute, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Concerning upcoming elections and re-elections.
- Medgar's Fund, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Photos, pamphlets concerning the Fayette Experiment and Charles Evans, and a newsletter.
- Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund. Educational Grants, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  Report on educational grants on the scholastic years of 1969 - 1970 and 1970 - 1971.
- Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Incorporated, 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Pamphlets, reports, and newsletters
- Miscellaneous, 1967-1972 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Resolutions and Reports, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  David Dubinsky Foundation resolutions
- Rural Advancement Fund, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  Correspondence and a proposal
- Schedule of Awards 1969 - 75, 1969-1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  Copies of these schedules throughout these years.
- Stern Family Fund, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  A report on the grants approved by the Stern Family Fund from March 1968 to March 1969
- The "Tyler" Project and Oil Portrait, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  Miscellaneous correspondence about "The Year Labor Earned Respect" stamps and an offer for an oil portrait of David Dubinsky.
- University of Wisconsin - Madison. Industrial Relations Research Institute, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  Announcement of Graduate Study
- U.S. Peoples Fund for the United Nations, Incorporated, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Correspondence and photos
- Voter Education Project (VEP), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  1976 Annual Report
- Women's Campaign Fund, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Memo about a fund-raising event entitled "Women in Power."
- 1975 Awards. A. Philip Randolph Institute (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Letter from the David Dubinsky Foundation awarding a grant and a report of a summary of activities.
- 1975 Awards. Agenda for Meeting [Part 1 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Agendas and information about the meetings that took place between 1975 and 1976.
- 1975 Awards. Agenda for Meeting [Part 2 of 2], 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 1975 Awards. Clearinghouse on Women's Issues, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Thank you correspondence, reports, and fact sheets.
- 1975 Awards. Consumer Federation of America (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Thank you correspondence, Wallstreet Journal articles, and an annual report.
- 1975 Awards. Foundation Biography, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Correspondence regarding information on the David Dubinsky Foundation.
- 1975 Awards. General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Appeals and thank you correspondence.
- 1975 Awards. Hispanic Organizations, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Correspondence, memos, and reports.
- 1975 Awards. Hunter College Center for Policy through Participation (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Thank you correspondence
- 1975 Awards. Labor's Stake in a Changing World Economy, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  Correspondence regarding planning of this national conference.
- 1975 Awards. Mail Ballot, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  Correspondence and reports
- 1975 Awards. Mexican American Legal Defense and Education Fund (MALDEF), 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  Correspondence, reports, pamphlets, and newsletters.
- 1975 Awards. Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Miscellaneous correspondence on minor inquiries regarding the 1975 meeting.
- 1975 Awards. National Academy of Popular Music, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Regarding the project on a Labor Songs Archive in the Academy's Songwriters Hall of Fame.
- 1975 Awards. National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, Incorporated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Appeal to the foundation.
- 1975 Awards. National Council of Negro Women (Box 4, Folder 16)
  Appeal to the foundation for child services project. Includes an informational brochure on the subject at hand.
- 1975 Awards. New America (Box 4, Folder 17)
  Summary of activities
- 1975 Awards. Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  Agenda for the January 15th 1976 meeting, list of organizations, litigation history, request for re-funding, and copies of New York Times articles regarding Puerto Rican-Americans.
- 1975 Awards. Recipients, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  List of grant recipients and correspondence from them.
- 1975 Awards. Requests [Part 1 of 2], 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  Funding proposals, reports, and correspondence from various organizations.
- 1975 Awards. Recipients [Part 2 of 2], 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- 1975 Awards. Rural Advancement Fund and the National Sharecropper's Fund, 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Appeals, reports, newspapers, and pamphlets.
- 1975 Awards. Universidad Boricua, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  Newspapers, reports, and appeals.
- 1975 Awards. University of Wisconsin-Madison Report (Box 4, Folder 24)
  Grant reports from the university's Industrial Relations Research Institute
- 1975 Awards. Voter Education Project, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Appeal and funding proposal.
- 1975 Awards. Women's Lobby, Incorporated, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Report
- 1975 Awards. Workers Defense League (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Report on the Employee Protection Program and news pamphlet.
- 1975 Awards. Youth Committee for Peace and Democracy in the Middle East (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Correspondence, report on activities, pamphlets, a bibliography, and a newsletter.
- The Christophers, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Correspondence, newspaper article, and a report regarding boycott to support the United Farm Workers of America. Includes a folder regarding information about the Christophers.
- Citizens' Research Foundation, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Thank you correspondence, appeals, reports, pamphlets, and exhibits.
- Consumer Help Project, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Annual report
- Coro Foundation, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Correspondence, reports, and proposals.
- Council on Religion and International Affairs, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  A report on the Corporate Consultation Program
- First Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Agendas, invitations, minutes, and correspondence from the first meeting.
- General Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Thank you correspondence, appeals, general information. Includes reports, photos, and various organizations.
- General Requests, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Appeals and reports from various organizations.
- ILGWU Legal Department, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Report to the General Executive Board on the activities of the legal department.
- Jack Barbash, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Correspondence to Jack Barbash
- National Council of Negro Women, Incorporated, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Thank you correspondence, information on activities, and appeals.
- Operation Southern Justice, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Project by the Roger Baldwin Foundation of the American Civil Liberties Union. Appeal, report, and financial statement given to the foundation.
- Second Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  Copies of schedule of awards, notes, agendas, newspaper articles, and minutes from the second meeting of the foundation.
- Sponsors for Educational Opportunity, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  End of the year report
- 1968 - 1972 Schedule of Awards (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Copies of the schedule of awards
- 1968 Awards. Recipients, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Correspondence
- 1970 Awards. Agenda (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Correspondence regarding the 1970 meeting.
- 1970 Awards. Aspira (Box 5, Folder 4)
  "Justica" newspaper and 1968 - 1970 annual reports.
- 1970 Awards. Awards (Box 5, Folder 5)
  List of organizations that were awarded grants.
- 1970 Awards. Board of Trustees Meeting (Box 5, Folder 6)
  Correspondence about the upcoming meeting.
- 1970 Awards. East Harlem Tenants Council, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Concerning a summer program called "Out of the Ghetto"
- 1970 Awards. Mail Ballots, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  Interorganizational requests for votes and information on past requests and allocations.
- 1970 Awards. Minutes of the Fourth Meeting (Box 5, Folder 9)
  List of schedules, notes, and summaries of the fourth meeting of the foundation.
- 1970 Awards. National Council of Negro Women, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Thank you correspondence, newspaper, and an invitation to attend the Mary McLeod Bethune Commemoration Celebration.
- 1970 Awards. Non-Recipients [Part 1 of 2], 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Correspondence between the foundation and various rejected organizations. Includes reports from the various organizations.
- 1970 Awards. Non-Recipients [Part 2 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 1970 Awards. Pace College. Edward Corsi Labor-Management Relations Institute, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 1970 Awards. Recipients [Part 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Correspondence awarding grants.
- 1970 Awards. Recipients [Part 2 of 2] (Box 5, Folder 15)
- 1970 Awards. Requests (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Appeals to the foundations. Includes proposals and reports.
- 1970 Awards. Sponsors for Educational Opportunity (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Concerning the Esso community
- 1970 Awards. University of Wisconsin-Madison. Industrial Relations Research Institute (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Copies of report on the use of the David Dubinsky Foundation grant
- 1970 Awards. Workers Defense League (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Concerning the FUND for HUMAN RIGHTS, Inc.
- American Council for Emigres in the Professions (ACEP), 1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  A letter about what was done with the grant money.
- Aspira, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Synopsis of program's success
- CCNY Institute for Social History (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Thank you correspondence. Undated
- Compass, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Appeal to the foundation, including a five-year projection.
- Consumer Federation of America, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Appeal to the foundation, a packet, and a copy of newspaper articles.
- Consumer Help Project, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  Project conducted by New York University and WNET/TV Channel 13. Includes a report requested by the foundation.
- Frontlash, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Includes a memorandum, report, and a newsletter.
- Georgetown University, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Proposal, annual report, and "Alternative Perspectives on Labor's Foreign Policy" report
- Hudson Guild, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Hunter College Center for Policy through Participation, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  Appeal for a grant
- Inter American University of Puerto Rico, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Regarding Dr. Clarence O. Senior
- League for Industrial Democracy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Workers Defense League, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Regarding Employee Protection Program
- Mexican American Legal Defense and Educational Fund, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  Thank you correspondence, newsletter, and report.
- National Council of Negro Women, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Invitation Ticket to the Mary McLeod Bethune Memorial Dedication
- New America, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Report on activities and newspapers.
- The New Direction, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  Report on current activities.
- Pace University. The Samuel Gompers Papers, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Regarding a Samuel Gompers project
- Puerto Rican Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Appeal to the foundation and a report
- Radio Liberty Committee, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Regarding the samzidat archive project entitled "Collection of Samizdat Documents"
- Roosevelt University, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Letter from the president of the university.
- Rural Advancement Fund, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Information about this organization, news clippings, and an appeal to the foundation.
- Taxation with Representation, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  Correspondence. Includes a newsletter containing the organization's annual report
- University of Wisconsin-Madison. Industrial Relations Research Institute, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  Brief report on how the grant was used.
- Youth Institute for Peace in the Middle East, Incorporated, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  Regarding a special emergency campaign
- 10th Year Proposal Mail Ballot, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  This year was the 10th year of the foundation, and the 85th birthday of David Dubinsky. Proposal for a commemoration.
- 1971 Awards. Minutes of the Fifth Meeting (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Copies of the minutes of this meeting.
- 1972 Awards. Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Thank you correspondence from many of the organization recipients.
- 1973 Awards. Agenda, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Includes list of organizations, memos, and correspondence.
- 1973 Awards. Council on Religion and International Affairs (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Includes two annual reports and one entitled "A New World Order: The Role of the Transnational Organization."
- 1973 Awards. Requests [Part 1 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Proposals, appeals, memos, reports, and correspondence from various organizations.
- 1973 Awards. Requests [Part 2 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 7)
- 1973 Awards. Schedule of Awards [Part 1 of 2], 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Copies of the list of 1973 awards from the January 16, 1974 board of trustees meeting.
- 1973 Awards. Schedule of Awards [Part 2 of 2] (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Copies of the list of 1973 awards from the January 16, 1974 board of trustees meeting. Includes initial drafts of the schedule.
- 1974 Awards. Agenda [Part 1 of 2], 1975 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  A board of trustees meting in 1975 regarding the winners from 1974.
- 1974 Awards. Agenda [Part 2 of 2], 1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- 1974 Awards. Aspira, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Correspondence and 1971 - 1972 annual report.
- 1974 Awards. Correspondence, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  Outgoing correspondence regarding the grant that the recipients will receive. Includes a list of the 1974 winners.
- 1974 Awards. Minutes of the Eight Meeting, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  Meeting concerning the 1974 budgets.
- 1974 Awards. Reports [Part 1 of 2], 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  Various reports, including newsletters and pamphlets.
- 1974 Awards. Reports [Part 2 of 2], 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- 1975 Awards. Announcement (Box 6, Folder 17)
  Outgoing correspondence regarding the 1975 awards.
- 1975 Awards. Mail Ballot (Box 6, Folder 18)
  Voting ballots and correspondence.
- 1975 Awards. Meeting Postponement (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Outgoing correspondence.
- 1975 Awards. Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 20)
  Newspapers, copies of articles, and correspondence.
- 1975 Awards. Recipients (Box 6, Folder 21)
  Thank you correspondence from various organizations. Includes newspapers and articles about the awards.
- 1975 Awards. Recipients, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 1975 Awards. Rejects (Box 6, Folder 23)
  Correspondence regarding rejections to appeals from various organizations.
- 1975 Awards. Requests (Box 6, Folder 24)
  Appeals to the foundation
- 1976 Awards. Agenda (Box 6, Folder 25)
  List of organizations, agendas, memos, and correspondence.
- 1976 Awards. Rejects (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  Letter about joint presentation of the Smithsonian Institution's Festival of American Folk Life.
- American Association of Junior Colleges (Box 6, Folder 28)
  Proposal. Undated.
- American Council for Emigres in the Professions, Incorporated (ACEP), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  Regarding Dr. Alvin Johnson, co-founder of ACEP.
- American Veterans Committee, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  Requested address and newspaper clipping
- Clearinghouse on Women's Issues [Part 1 of 2], 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  Information about the organization.
- Clearinghouse on Women's Issues [Part 2 of 2], 1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  Bylaws of the Association
- 1969 Awards. A. Philip Randolph Educational Fund (Box 7, Folder 1)
- 1969 Awards. Agenda (Box 7, Folder 2)
  List and summaries of requests.
- 1969 Awards. Allocations and Requests (Box 7, Folder 3)
- 1969 Awards. Board of Trustees Meeting, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Includes reports, proposals, and copies of various newspaper articles.
- 1969 Awards. Bund Archives of the Jewish Labor Movement (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Part of the Atran Center for Jewish Culture.
- 1969 Awards. Conference on Labor and the Migrant [Part 1 of 3], 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Sent as a report to the foundation.
- 1969 Awards. Conference on Labor and the Migrant [Part 2 of 3], 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- 1969 Awards. Conference on Labor and the Migrant [Part 3 of 3], 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- 1969 Awards. Cornell University. Industrial and Labor Relations School (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Rough draft of a proposal to the foundation.
- 1969 Awards. David Shub Book Committee (Box 7, Folder 10)
  Appeal for grant for the creation of a second volume on David Shub's memoirs.
- 1969 Awards. Filing (Box 7, Folder 11)
  Includes various correspondence and a report by the National Council of Negro Women called "Hunger."
- 1969 Awards. Gus Tyler Notes (Box 7, Folder 12)
  Regarding previous award recipients and organizations requesting grants.
- 1969 Awards. Lower East Side Community Ambassadors (Box 7, Folder 13)
  Appeal to the foundation, including a brief of the program's success.
- 1969 Awards. Mail Ballots to be charged against awards., 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  Includes a summary of requests, letters addressed to Louis Stulberg, and mail ballots concerning the Edward Corsi Foundation, National Council of Negro Women, and the Beth Israel Fund.
- 1969 Awards. Medgar Evers Fund (Box 7, Folder 15)
  Appeal to the foundation for a grant to support its seed money.
- 1969 Awards. Minutes of the Third Meeting (Box 7, Folder 16)
- 1969 Awards. Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 17)
  various correspondence.
- 1969 Awards. National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing (Box 7, Folder 18)
  Appeal to the foundation and current statistics brief.
- 1969 Awards. National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  Regarding legal defense fund and campaign to end capital punishment through court action.
- 1969 Awards. Schedule of Awards (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Copies
- 1969 Awards. Sponsors for Educational Opportunity (Box 7, Folder 21)
  Appeal for increased support from the foundation due to the increasing number of students sponsored by the program.
- 1969 Awards. University of Illinois. College of Law (Box 7, Folder 22)
  Requesting a grant renewal
- 1969 Awards. University of Wisconsin-Madison. Industrial Relations Research Institute, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  Proposal
- 1969 Awards. U.S. People's Fund of the United Nations (Box 7, Folder 24)
  Appeal to the foundation and reports.
- 1969 Awards. U.S. Youth Council (Box 7, Folder 25)
  Organizing Conference for Youth and Students objectives.
- American Council Emigres in the Professions (ACEP), 1970 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  Reports
- Coro Foundation, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  Outline of Fellow's assignment locations.
- Foreign Policy, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Concerning the 1976 Democratic campaign and the Middle East
- General Correspondence [Part 1 of 2], 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- General Correspondence [Part 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Hispanic Recipients, 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  Correspondence regarding Hispanic organizations.
- Imports, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  Regarding delegations from Connecticut and Rhode Island to visit with Congress people on November 19th to discuss imports.
- Institute of International Community Action (Box 7, Folder 33)
  Regarding a proposed publication entitled "Spes Mundi." Undated.
- Kellwood Corporation, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  Regarding ILGWU's 10-year battle against the Kellwood Corporation in Little Rock, Arkansas
- League of Women Voters (Box 7, Folder 35)
  Day Care Pamphlets. Undated.
- Location of ILGWU Local Unions, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  Addresses of unions.
- "The Many-Sided Mr. Meany", 1970 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  An article by John Corry that appeared in Harper's Magazine. It criticizes George Meany.
- Memos and notes, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  Handwritten notes and a notepad.
- Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 39)
- The New Direction, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  Pamphlets
- Reports, Proposals, and Summaries [Part 1 of 4], 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  From various organizations requesting a grant or a looking for a renewal.
- Reports, Proposals, and Summaries [Part 2 of 4], 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Reports, Proposals, and Summaries [Part 3 of 4], 1973-1975 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Reports, Proposals, and Summaries [Part 4 of 4], 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- 1970 Awards. Articles, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  "Justice" newspaper article about the 1970 foundation awards.
- 1970 Awards. East Harlem Tenants Council, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Inter-office Communication
- 1971 Awards. A. Philip Randolph Institute (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Appeal to the foundation to finance the institute's third conference.
- 1971 Awards. Agenda [Part 1 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Agenda for the fourth meeting, and lists of organizations and summaries.
- 1971 Awards. Agenda [Part 2 of 2] (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 1971 Awards. Alliance of Latin Art (Box 8, Folder 6)
  Appeal to the foundation for sponsorship.
- 1971 Awards. American Council for Emigres in the Professions (Box 8, Folder 7)
  Regarding refugee professionals.
- 1971 Awards. Aspira (Box 8, Folder 8)
  Appeal to the foundation. Includes an annual progress report.
- 1971 Awards. Award Letters (Box 8, Folder 9)
- 1971 Awards. Board of Trustees Meeting (Box 8, Folder 10)
  Announcement
- 1971 Awards. Cornell University. Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 8, Folder 11)
  Appeal to the foundation and proposed curriculum.
- 1971 Awards. Council of Higher Educational Institutions (Box 8, Folder 12)
  Article ideas for the "Federationist."
- 1971 Awards. Frontlash (Box 8, Folder 13)
  Appeal to the foundation
- 1971 Awards. League of Women Voters (Box 8, Folder 14)